Hey Vicky, this is a video to thank you for the sound healing experience that you gave us a couple of days back.
I must share with you that the experience was very very very deep.
I didn't go into a very deep, extremely relaxed state.
I really didn't want to open my eyes and come back.
So thank you for the experience and I think for me the major shift, there was a shift that happened,
which is apart from going deep.
I think for me one of the shifts that I find after that sound healing session is the belief in self,
especially at a time that I've got so much to do.
I think it's very common for us to have these questions.
Will I be able to do it?
How will I be able to do it?
But for me the belief is back and I attribute it to your sound healing session.
Thank you so much and I really wish a lot more people experience your magic
and in addition to the sound healing just your presence and the way you guide us through it is absolutely magical.
Thank you so much.